Inventory of the Michael Blinov collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Society of the Russian Veterans of World War I, Inc., and Russian All-Military Union, San Francisco, 1869-1984 (Box 2-16, 20)
  - Krivosheev, Leonid Andreevich, Director of the Museum of the Leib-Gvardii Volynskii regiment
    - Khodnev, Dmitrii. "Leib-Gvardii Finliandskii polk v srazhenii pod Leiptsigom (4.X.1813-4.X. 1963)," manuscript, undated (Folder 13: 16)
    - Postcards and prints depicting icons and the island of Corfu, 1938-1962 (Folder 13: 17)
    - Correspondence, albums with views of Holy Land, and holograph poems relating to religious matters, 1916-1927 (Folder 14: 1)
    - Obshchestvo ofitserov Leib-Gvardii Volynskogo polka
      - Correspondence with the Romanov royal family
        - Grand Duchess Anastasiia Nikolaevna, 1927-1929 (Folder 14: 2)
        - Grand Dukes Vladimir Kirillovich, Kirill Vladimirovich, Andrei Vladimirovich, Nikolai Nikolaevich, Aleksandr Ol'denburgskii; Grand Duchesses Kseniia Nikolaevna, Ol'ga Nikolaevna, and Elena Vladimirovna, 1916-1976 (Folder 14: 3)
          Includes orders for Volynskii polk
        - Grand Duchesses Vera Konstantinovna and Elena Vladimirovna, 1938-1959 (Folder 14: 4)
      - Grand Duke Vladimir Kirillovich, family photograph, 1975 (Folder 14: 5)
      - Court of Honor files
        - Colonel Kashkin, 1924-1959 (Folder 14: 6)
          Includes list of documents of the Court of Honor and correspondence
        - Colonel I. P. Petrushevskii, 1924-1925 (Folder 14: 7)
        - Staff-Captain V.A. Porai-Koshits and Second Leutenant Mikhail Meder, 1925-1927 (Folder 14: 8)
        - Staff-Captain Pyshnov and Second Leutenant S. Iankovskii file; Captain A. N. Podramentsev; Colonel N. L Neelov; General L. I.Kir'ianov, 1925-1927 (Folder 14: 9)
        - Colonel Viskovskii, 1923-1925 (Folder 14: 10-11)
          Includes list of documents in the file
      - Komitet po sboru pozhervovanii na sooruzhenie khrama-pamiatnika na pole Leiptsigskogo srazhenia, 1913 (Folder 14: 12)
        Includes correspondence and memoirs about èmigrè life in Serbia
      - Deputy Chairman of the Society of Officers of the Volynskii Regiment in Yugoslavia, book of orders, 1938-1940 (Folder 14: 13)
      - Minutes of general meetings, 1917-1940 (Folder 14: 14-15)
    - Obzor deiatel'nosti Obshchestva popecheniia o bol'nykh i ranenykh, 1877 (Folder 15: 1)
    - Leib-Gvardii Volynskii polk file, 1869-1911 (Folder 15: 2-9)
      Includes military orders, drill inspection reports, court-martial sentences, financial documents
    - Warsaw military district, military orders, 1885-1902 (Folder 15: 10)
    - Tret'ia Gvardeiskaia pekhotnaia diviziia, military orders, 1869-1911 (Folder 15: 11-12)
    - Andreev, Vladimir Vladimirovich, personal papers, 1919-1940 (Folder 16: 1)
    - Arkhangel'skii, Aleksei Petrovich, General, Chair of the Russian All-Military Union
      - Correspondence relating to General A. P. Arkhangel'skii, 1959-1960 (Folder 16: 2)
      - Obituaries, with related correspondence, 1955-1960 (Folder 16: 3-4)
    - Istomin, Konstantin Efstafievich, photographs, 1952-1976 (Folder 16: 5)
- Ark, Peter Aleksander (Petr Aleksandrovich Arkad'ev), personal papers and photographs, 1904-1974 (Box 16: 6)
- Leontieff, Evgenii Aleksandrovich, 1895-1984 (Box 16-19)
  - Autobiography, undated (Folder 16: 7)
  - Correspondence
    - Family members, 1921-1977 (Folder 16: 8)
    - Borel, Miguel C., 1960-1965 (Folder 16: 9)
    - Osipov, Michail M., 1971-1978 (Folder 16: 10)
    - Pavlov, Boris, 1984 (Folder 16: 11)
      Includes articles on General Andreev, with related corrspondence
    - Prokofiev, A., 1960-1978 (Folder 16: 12)
    - Sturmer, Roman, Father, 1977 March 2 (Folder 16: 13)
    - Walter (Vasil'ev), V. B., 1975-1976 (Folder 16: 14)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1930-1984 (Folder 16: 15-16)
  - "Vospominaniya generala ot infanterii Yakova Fedorovicha Shkinskogo, byvshego kommandira voisk irkutskogo voennogo okruga," memoirs
    - Bound manuscripts, 1922 (Folder 17: 1-7)
    - Bound manuscripts, undated (Folder 18: 1-5)
    - Supplemental material, 1877/1878 (Folder 19: 1)
      Includes maps
  - Polozhenie o shkole soldatskikh detei Leib-Gvardii Volynskogo polka, regulations, 1895 May 1 (Folder 19-2)
  - Soiuz Gallipoliitsev
    - Correspondence, 1923/1974 (Folder 19: 3)
    - Vrangel', Petr Nikolaievich, 1920/1928 (Folder 19: 4)
      Contains correspondence, mostly with General Evgenii Karlovich Miller
    - Levitskii, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich, obituaries, 1970 (Folder 19: 5)
    - Report on library activities, 1924-1925 (Folder 19: 6)
    - Russian troops in Gallipoli, photographs and postcardsli, undated (Folder 19: 7)
  - Printed matter
    - Artilleriiskii vestnik, 1932-1938 (Folder 19: 8)
    - Gallipoliiskii vestnik (Vestnik gallipoliitsev), 1937-1938 (Folder 19: 9)
    - Gallipoliets (Vestnik obshchestva gallipoliitsev), 1935-1971 (Folder 19: 10-11)
    - Rodina, Russkii invalid, 1964-1972 (Folder 19: 12)
    - "Spravochnaia kniga gvardeiskogo ob'edineniia", 1938-1962 (Folder 19: 13)
      Includes Biulleten' ob'edinenia Leib-Gvardii Moskovskogo polka